Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Are you all right?
You weren't hypnotized by me.
You already had so many
strange things going on before.
Logically speaking,
I shouldn't be so defenseless.
Why force Shen Changfeng's grandmother to her death?
She's just an old woman.
Her death
shouldn't be blamed on me.
I only asked her for a favor.
Changfeng really left.
I believe what you said.
But I truly have urgent business with him.
Please come with me.
If he avoids me, fine.
But he can't
ignore his own grandmother, right?
Who are you, really?
Don't hurt others in this village
just for your grandson.
I'll wait for you here.
Okay.
I'll go inside and get something.
Even giving my all, I can't do it.
Throwing my life to shake the world,
no regrets.
Trying my best is still in vain.
In this rotten world,
how is there a fool like you?
Dying quietly, like an ant.
Xiulan.
Why is it you?
That's how most humans are.
But sadly,
after so many Seven Stars Dreams,
and resolving so many dying obsessions,
you still don't understand.
Humans
are so weak,
and such a dull existence.
You're the best at pretending.
Weak.
The lingering love in mortal flesh
can shake life and death like a firefly's glow.
That's what lights the Seven Stars Lamp.
These bits of love gather into light,
carrying joy and sorrow,
illuminating the River of Forgetfulness.
Can't you see it?
The world before your eyes
exists because of this.
My fault.
Why say so much?
You can't even
see the Seven Stars Dream,
what do you know?
Fuyi.
You shouldn't make things so complicated.
Or what?
Should I just lie down
and let you kill me?
No.
Don't cry.
No, don't scare me.
No.
Wake up.
Prince.
Prince, where are you?
He Fuyi, someone's here.
Prince.
He Fuyi.
Zhenhuan Biaoju.
She was the only survivor back then.
She might know something.
If she dares to disobey,
losing an arm or leg doesn't matter.
As long as she can talk.
Yes, sir.
I'll have the palace staff handle it.
This is no small matter.
If anything goes wrong,
even you, Xiao Wu,
I won't show mercy.
So,
are you still going?
Baiyintu is willing to serve the Empress Dowager.
He Fuyi of Zhenhuan Biaoju,
entrusted by another,
came to collect Liu Chunru's body.
It's you.
I really found you.
He Fuyi.
Head Escort He.
You...
really are...
Well,
the fish is cooked.
Logically speaking,
this feeling
should be a flutter of the heart.
Right?
That's right.
Flutter of the heart.
Don't cry.
That day,
I lay alone in the cold grass.
I was truly, truly scared.
I knew I was about to die.
But in my mind,
only one wild thought appeared.
I hoped someone would come stay with me.
He Fuyi.
That day, you didn't just save my life,
you also fulfilled my obsession.
Fuyi.
You must stay safe.
That's my obsession now.
No.
A Qi.
I'm counting on you.
No.
Don't scare me.
The Way has no beginning or end.
All things have life and death.
Fuyi.
This is the fate of mortals.
But you still have a chance
to go with me.
Heaven and earth
endure for so long
and last so long
because they do not live for themselves.
So they can live long.
Heaven's law is like me.
My law is like heaven.
My fate is in my hands,
not in the heavens.
Seven Stars descends upon the child
to protect his body
The Seven Stars' aura gathers as one
above the crown of the head
three feet above the head
When one does good
the star shines bright and large
When one does evil
the star dims and shrinks
Good deeds bring fortune
Evil deeds bring disaster
When the starlight fades
the body
perishes
Master
Your cultivation
is still far from complete
He Fuyi
Can you hear me
The seven stars above are answering me
A Qi
From the first time you met him
you said his scent felt familiar
It's because my blood runs in his veins
Is that right
Yes
Now all seven Beidou of the Seven Stars Lamp are lit
This is what Master sought
the true power of the Seven Stars Lamp
A Qi
You can revive Baiyintu, right
Yes
As long as he still breathes
I can make him
just like I did for you
But
this power isn't limitless
If I save him
He Fuyi
you'll have only two years left to live
A Qi
I'm counting on you
Alright then
Don't move
I can only bring you back
Your wounds will heal slowly
What did you do
Logically speaking
this is the best deal
Are you crazy
Trading your life for my twelve years
That's not a damn deal
Didn't the doctor tell you to rest in bed
I need to write to my father and mother
to tell them I'm marrying you
What nonsense are you saying
Who's talking nonsense
I only have twelve years to live
And you
only have two years left
How can we not hurry and do what's important
Gathering Spirit Aura quickly
is what matters most
Whether it's long years
or fleeting moments
I want to stay by your side always
Whether it's long years
or fleeting moments
It all depends on me, A Qi
Who says otherwise
Little living ancestor
Prince
The Prince Ning's manor sent someone
Tell me
Prince Ning invites you to a banquet tomorrow
What's the reason
Who cares what he wants
Going now
will surely attract the Empress Dowager's attention
Can't we just not go
You all
I haven't tried all the good food yet
Ancestor
This time, we really have to run
Before, I could use my injury as an excuse
Now they've lost all patience
Whether it's Prince Ning or the Empress Dowager
we can't afford to offend either
If we don't run
we're doomed
Looks like my fate is to always be on the run
I'll be counting on you from now on
Prince
Let's get ready to leave
Head Escort He
Didn't expect it so soon
There's already a new Seven Stars Dream
Yeah
This isn't looking good
We still have to run
What's wrong
Blessings to the Empress Dowager
It's the Empress Dowager's dream